You don’t really know
Who you’re going with
But you can’t catch a breath
Before you’re going in
Hold onto the ride
Cause you know it’s really gonna spin
You know that I’ll be here to catch you
But please don’t fall again
Hey I could’ve messed up
When I hit the wrong side
But baby we done bounced back
Now we’re with right type
Standing with your tongue tied
I know what that feels like
Better get a grip cause ya really
Just want to hold tight
You should really probably
Sort this out
But you know I’d never let you down
But picking you back up
Isn’t as easy as it sounds
But fuck I do it anyway
Damn it’s just another day
Thinking they could stop me now
They better find another way
This ain’t just some game we play
Get that shit up out my face
They’re not stressed cause I’m the one that’s making sure we’re here to stay
Here to stay
We’ll really make it out somehow
You know I’ll help you sort this out
I’ll never let you fall back down
Hey I could’ve messed up
When I hit the wrong side
But baby we done bounced back
Now we’re with right type
Standing with your tongue tied
I know what that feels like
Better get a grip cause ya really
Just want to hold tight
Hey I could’ve messed up
When I hit the wrong side
But baby we done bounced back
Now we’re with right type
Standing with your tongue tied
I know what that feels like
Better get a grip cause ya really
Just want to hold tight